*  Bands Concerts Venues Locations Bucket Lists Users

Privacy Policy
==============

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Concert Archives website and apps and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Concert Archives includes the Concert Archives website and apps. Concert Archives is owned and operated by Thiele Unlimited LLC d/b/a Concert Archives. By using Concert Archives, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Collection of your Personal Information
---------------------------------------

In order to better provide you with products and services offered, Concert Archives may collect personally identifiable information, such as your:

* Email Address
* Username
* Location

We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services. These may include: (a) registering for an account; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when purchasing products and services. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Use of your Personal Information
--------------------------------

Concert Archives collects and uses your personal information to operate and deliver the services you have requested.

Concert Archives may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Concert Archives and its affiliates.

Sharing Information with Third Parties  

Concert Archives may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (email, username, location) is transferred to the third party. Concert Archives may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Concert Archives, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Concert Archives may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Concert Archives or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Concert Archives; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Concert Archives, or the public.

Concert Archives is affiliated with Publisher First, Inc. d/b/a Freestar for the purposes of placing advertising on Concert Archives, and Freestar will collect and use certain data for advertising purposes. To learn more about Freestar’s data usage, click here: [https://freestar.com/privacy-policy/](https://freestar.com/privacy-policy/). Concert Archives maintains a list of companies that provide [advertising](https://www.concertarchives.org/ads.txt) and [affiliate](https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1i9JbbzcIHIoq9njq9DH_F5C3ZGH0lEqEi4ELqsYUZSo/edit?usp=sharing) services to us.

Concert Archives uses YouTube API Services which are subject to the [Google Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Opt-Out of Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties
--------------------------------------------------------------

In connection with any personal information we may disclose to a third party for a business purpose, you have the right to know:

* The categories of personal information that we disclosed about you for a business purpose.

You have the right under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (CCPA) and certain other privacy and data protection laws, as applicable, to opt-out of the disclosure of your personal information. If you exercise your right to opt-out of the disclosure of your personal information, we will refrain from disclosing your personal information, unless you subsequently provide express authorization for the disclosure of your personal information. To opt-out of the disclosure of your personal information click “Opt Out” in the footer of the website.

Security of your Personal Information
-------------------------------------

Concert Archives secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Concert Archives uses SSL Encryption for this purpose.

We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.

Right to Deletion
-----------------

Subject to certain exceptions set out below, on receipt of a verifiable request from you, we will:

* Delete your personal information from our records; and
* Direct any service providers to delete your personal information from their records.

Please note that we may not be able to comply with requests to delete your personal information if it is necessary to:

* Complete the transaction for which the personal information was collected, fulfill the terms of a written warranty or product recall conducted in accordance with federal law, provide a good or service requested by you, or reasonably anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship with you, or otherwise perform a contract between you and us;
* Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity; or prosecute those responsible for that activity;
* Debug to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality;
* Exercise free speech, ensure the right of another consumer to exercise his or her right of free speech, or exercise another right provided for by law;
* Comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act;
* Engage in public or peer-reviewed scientific, historical, or statistical research in the public interest that adheres to all other applicable ethics and privacy laws, when our deletion of the information is likely to render impossible or seriously impair the achievement of such research, provided we have obtained your informed consent;
* Enable solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with your expectations based on your relationship with us;
* Comply with an existing legal obligation; or
* Otherwise use your personal information, internally, in a lawful manner that is compatible with the context in which you provided the information.

Children Under Thirteen
-----------------------

Concert Archives does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this application.

Disconnecting your Concert Archives Account from Third Party Websites
---------------------------------------------------------------------

You will be able to connect your Concert Archives account to third party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR CONCERT ARCHIVES ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED IN THIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. Users may disconnect their accounts from third-party websites on their "Settings" page.

Opt-Out & Unsubscribe from Third Party Communications
-----------------------------------------------------

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from third-party partners of Concert Archives by emailing us [\[email protected\]](https://www.concertarchives.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Email Communications
--------------------

From time to time, Concert Archives may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication. In order to improve our Services, we may receive a notification when you open an email from Concert Archives or click on a link therein.

If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from Concert Archives, you may opt out of such communications unsubscribing from email newsletters and notifications on your 'Account Settings' page.

External Data Storage Sites
---------------------------

We may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted. Concert Archives maintains a list of [sub-processors who provide data services to us](https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/16OtfEv26HEEW2YfRkP4nRs_OZ5PaYcJv6JfAQCRTvWw/edit?usp=sharing).

Changes to this Statement
-------------------------

Concert Archives reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our application, and/or by updating any privacy information. Your continued use of the application and/or Services available after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.

Contact Information
-------------------

Concert Archives welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Concert Archives has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Concert Archives at:

Thiele Unlimited LLC d/b/a Concert Archives  
PO Box 2572  
Vancouver, Washington 98668

Email Address:  
[\[email protected\]](https://www.concertarchives.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Telephone number:  
(415) 894-5070

Last updated June 17, 2023

### As Seen On:

* 
* 
* 
* 
* 
* 

### The concert database for fans, by fans.

#### Resources

#### Legal

* © Copyright 2013 - 2024 [Concert Archives](http://thieleunlimited.com/)

#### Company

Share / Cite

Share or Cite This Page: ×

Page URL

 Copy

Page Title

 Copy

Get our logo & icon: [concertarchives.zip](https://www.concertarchives.org/assets/logos/concert-archives-logos.zip)

### Cited by Thousands Including:

* 
* 
* 
* 
* 
*
